Pull yourself together.
정신 차려요
Do you want to die on your first day?
입대 하는 날 죽고 싶어요
Do it now.
바로 지금
Get crushed!
부숴버릴 거야
You must live on.
당신은 살아남아야 해요
What is going on here?
이게 도대체 어떻게 된 일이야
Do not let go of the RED Strings.
놓지 마세요…레드 스트링스를 놓지 마세요
Good morning.
안녕
The weather is great today.
오늘은 하루 종일 좋은 날씨라던데요
We have no mission this morning.
오전에는 임무가 없어요
Would you go out with me? There's a place I want to visit.
나가볼래요 저 가고 싶은 곳이 있어서요
Baki!
밧키에요
SCARLET NEXUS
《스칼렛넥서》
♪A crime in reality♪
현실의 크라임
♪For Heaven's sake♪
For Heaven's sake
♪Accepts any fake♪
거짓을 용납하고
♪And disappears piling the eternity in fantasy♪
영원한 환상은 한겹한겹 사라진다
♪Won't take it at all, I get sick♪
완벽하진 않아요 I get sick
♪A girl looking back♪
돌아선 소녀는
♪Casts the miracle into this instant world♪
이 순간의 세상에서 기적을 남겼어요
♪Did you lie♪
Did you lie
♪Spit the venom♪
Spit the venom
♪I know why♪
I know why
♪I've found a game of ecstasy♪
최고의 게임을 찾았어요
♪Red Criminal gets life♪
Red Criminal gets life
♪I've never been in love♪
I've never been in love
♪Don't know when I started getting sick of this world♪
언제부터 이런 세상이 지겨워졌나요
♪We will fly♪
We will fly
♪Someday I won't be crying♪
Someday I won't be crying
♪I've been sacrificing myself not to hurt anybody♪
더 이상 상처받게 하지 않기 위해 자신을 희생했어요
SCARLET GUARDIANS
(스칼렛 가디언)
Up next, we have Other attack forecast for each province.
다음은 괴이성에서 보내 온 괴이예보입니다
The probability for Suoh Capital is 10%.
스오 근처에 출몰할 확률은 10%입니다
For Seiran, it's 15%.
세이란시 근처에 출몰할 확률은 15%입니다
The probability for Togetsu is 12%.
토게츠 지방 부근에 출몰할 확율은 12%입니다
"OTHERS TODAY" The Extinction Belt is at the stratosphere.
(오늘의 괴이) 단절의 띠는 세이소켄 부근에 있습니다
There is currently no impact on the surface.
현재는 지상에는 별 영향이 없습니다
There is a higher chance of it approaching certain areas in the afternoon.
오후에는 일부 지역에 접근할 가능성이 비교적 높습니다
-I think the person who saved me was Kasane. -Please stay cautious at all times.
-난 그 사람이 카사네인 것 같아 -주의하시기 바랍니다
How is that possible?
어떻게 그럴 수가 있어
But members of OSF might have stunted growth.
근데 토벌군 대원이라면 성장을 억제당했을 수도 있잖아
You have a point. Appearances can be deceptive in OSF.
그건 그래 토벌군의 겉모습만 봐서는 안돼
2nd Lieutenant Arashi Spring is the elder sister.
아라시 스프링 대위가 누나고
Major General Fubuki is the younger brother instead.
후부키 스프링 연대장이 오히려 그녀의 동생이라니
The age and the appearances have no direct relations.
외모는 연령과 무관하니까
So there is basically no need for honorific titles.
그래서 기본적으로 존칭 쓸 필요도 없고
Ignore the ranks and titles, what matters is true strength.
계급도 안 보고  실력만 있으면 된다고
Captain Seto said so himself.
세토 대장도 그렇게 말했잖아
But Kasane and Naomi are both amateurs just like us.
그래도 카사네와 나오미도 우리와 같은 신인이야
They are only 16 years old.
같은 열여섯살이라고
Even though Naomi is the elder sister,
나오미가 나보다 나이 많은 누나라고 해도
I'm not going to change my mind.
내 맘은 변함없으니까
I'm sorry to take up your time.
저와 함께 나오자고 해서 미안해요
If I let you go out alone, you might attract creeps.
언니를 혼자 나가게 하면 이상한 것들이 몰려올 수 있어요
All of us have powers.
우리 모두가 가지고 있는 '뇌능력'
Thanks to our powers,
이 힘의 덕분에
we cannot only access psynet
사이넷을 연결할 수 있을 뿐만 아니라
but also use it for many things
많은 일을 할 수 있어요
such as shopping.
물건을 살 수 있고요
PAYMENT COMPLETED
(결제완료)
We can search for information and send messages.
정보를 찾아볼 수 있고 메시지를 전달할 수 있어요
Some of us have power,
그중에서도 탁월한 두뇌능력을 가진 '초뇌능력'자들
they are the OSF.
그들이 바로 토벌군이에요
Scarlet Guardians!
스칼렛 가디언
Yakumo Sumeragi.
야쿠모 스메라기
He saved mankind from total annihilation with the Spring of Extinction.
'단절의 봄'으로 멸종될 뻔한 인류를 구한
He is the founding father of New Himuka.
뉴히무카의 건국의 아버지
A great man indeed.
역시 대단해
Your ancestor's grave is now a tourism destination.
자네 선조의 묘소가 지금 관광 명소로 되였다니
He was born over 2000 years ago.
그분은 2천 년 전의 사람이라서
So I don't feel any relation in particular.
별로 실감이 안나
There it is.
있네
BAKI TALISMAN
(밧키오미쿠지)
An omikuji event in collaboration with Baki.
밧키 콜라보 오미쿠지 이벤트네
Even the founding father is fashionable.
건국의 아버지도 시대를 따라가고 있군
Yuito, Nagi.
유이토 나기
Naomi and Kasane!
나오미 가사네
Are you here for the omikuji too?
너희들도 오미쿠지 뽑으러 왔어
I'm here with Yuito.
유이토 따라왔어
I ask Kasane to come with me.
난 가사네랑 같이 오자고 했어
Yuito, do you like Baki too?
유이토도 밧키를 좋아하세요
-Well... -Now that we are here,
-뭐 그냥... -참 잘 됐어
let's have some tea after this.
오미쿠지 뽑고 차 한잔하실래요
There is still some time before our mission this afternoon.
오후 임무를 시작하기까지는 아직 시간이 좀 남아있어
Sister, beware of this man.
언니 조심하세요
I knew I should have come with you.
역시 제가 따라오기 잘했어요
-Did I do something wrong? -Kasane...
-내가 뭘 했나 -카사네
What is it?
무슨 일이에요
Kasane, Naomi, do you have a sister that is much older than you?
카사네와 나오미외에 나이가 많은 언니가 있어
Kasane is my only sibling.
우리 집은 나와 카사네 두자매뿐이야
Do you have any relatives who joined OSF in the past?
친척중에 토벌군에 가담했던 사람이라든가
No. Why do you ask?
없어 그게 왜
Let's draw the omikuji now.
그보다 오미쿠지나 뽑자
Then we'll have some tea together!
빨리 뽑고 같이 차 마시러나 가자고
"GREAT DISASTER"
(대흉)
Sister, what did you get?
언니는 뭘 뽑았어요
Great prosperity.
대길이야
Everyone got the worst omikuji ever except for Naomi.
나오미 외에는 모두 대흉이네
At least not all of us will get bad luck.
전부 대흉보다는 낫잖아
But we have an OSF mission afterward.
그래도 그렇지 담방 토벌군의 임무를 수행해야 하는데
This is a bad omen.
너무 불길한 거 아니야
It's such a buzzkill.
기분 잡치네
Don't throw it away, Nagi.
나기 그걸 함부로 버려서는 안돼
Yuito!
유이토 너…
-Give it to me. -Sorry!
-줘봐 -미안 미안
Yuito and Nagi, give me yours.
유이토 것도 나기 것도 다 주세요
Tie it like this.
이렇게 묶어서
This should turn your bad luck into lesser good luck.
됐어 이러면 우리 운세가 소길쯤은 될 거야
Let's give it our best from now on.
이제부터 함께 힘내요
You are so gentle and kind, Naomi!
따뜻해 아오미는 정말 마음이 따뜻해요
Your kindness saved us all!
당신의 따뜻한 마음이 모두를 살릴 거예요
You saved me too! This is great!
저도 당신이 살린 거예요 너무 좋아
The Seiran front?
세이란 방면군이
Where is it this time?
이번엔 어디야
It's an abandoned underground railway line, it's near the Suoh Nine.
폐지하선로 스오 9호선 부근입니다
Just as we mentioned before,
전에 말한 바와 같이
they are going in to investigate the Other activity.
괴이한 걸 조사하기 위해서래요
They refuse to heed our advice despite the objection.
몇 번을 항의해도 그들은 듣지를 안는군
Send in backups.
경비 인원을 추가시켜
Yes. There's another report
네 그리고…
we have yet to verify.
아직 실증되지 않은 정보가 하나 더 있습니다
There are some suspicious activities in Togetsu.
토게츠에 수상한 움직임이 있는 것 같아요
The Moon is stirring up troubles again.
달을 믿는 성가신 놈들인가
I will report after the investigation has been completed.
정보가 확인되면 바로 보고드리겠습니다
I'll leave it to you.
자네한테 맡기겠네
Minister.
본부장...
No, Kaito.
아니 카이토
Yes.
네
How is Yuito doing?
유이토의 정황은 어때
I saw the report of him defeating an Other.
괴이를 때려눕혔다고 보도됐던데
I didn't get a chance to talk to him after he joined the army.
입대후 아직 그와 대화할 기회가 없었습니다
I know he is my brother, but I can't give him any special treatments.
비록 형제라고 해도 특별대우를 할 수는 없습니다
I see. You have a point.
그렇군 하긴
That's all for the report today.
오늘 보고는 여기까지 하겠습니다
I should leave now.
그럼 실례하겠습니다
The Seirans are on the move again.
세이란 쪽에 움직이기 시작한 것 같은데
Let them be.
마음대로 하게 내둬
What did I...
내가…도대체…
What's wrong, Yuito?
유이토 왜 그래
It's nothing.
괜찮아…
Everyone is here.
전부 다 왔는가
The joint beginner training of Seto Platoon and Kyoka Platoon
세토 소대와 쿄카 소대 신인들을 환영하기 위한 공동훈련
is about to begin.
시작할게요
A joint training?
공동훈련
The rule is simple.
규칙은 간단해
It's a 5v5 simulation battle between Seto Platoon and Kyoka Platoon.
세토 소대 다섯 명과 교카 소대 다섯 명의 모의전이다
The first team to secure the flag in the middle wins.
정중앙에 있는 저 깃발을 먼저 빼앗은 소대가 승리한다
There are only four in Kyoka Platoon.
교카 소대는 겨우 네 명뿐이네
Arashi!
아라시
Arashi, shutting down.
아라시 프로그램은 셧다운 됐어요
Don't fall asleep!
자지 마
She seems different from the TV.
평소 생각했던 아라시와는 다른 느낌이네요
When we saw her online and on the news...
인터넷이랑 티비에서 본 아라시는...
I will give it my best too!
아라시는 열심히 할 거예요
That's when she's at work.
그건 영업용이라고
What we see here is her usual self.
평소 아라시는 저런 모습이에요
People in the OSF call her Lazy Arashi.
토벌군에서는 그녀를 '노른자 아라시'라고 불러
Fine, let's get it over with.
할 수 없군 빨리 끝내야지
Okay, everyone.
자 각자 준비
Let's do our best.
힘내요
Okay.
네
It's done, Kasane.
다 됐어 카사네
This is the proof of our bond as sisters.
이건 나와 카사네가 자매임을 증명하는 거야
-Sister. What is it?
-언니 -왜
Are you concerned about Yuito?
혹시 유이토를 의식하고 있는거야
Kasane, what made you say that?
카사네 왜 갑자기 그런 말을 해
I'm not particularly concerned...
의식한다고 하기는…
I just find him a nice person.
그냥… 괜찮은 것 같아서…
Understood.
알랐어
Whether he is qualified to be with you,
언니하고 어울릴 만한 사람인지
I will find it out.
내가 직접 확인해 줄게
Kasane!
카사네
"MAJOR SHIDEN RITTER, POWER: ELECTROKINESIS" Young Master of the Sumeragi family.
(시덴 리터 중위 초뇌능력: 방전) 스메라기 일가의 도련님인가
"CAPTAIN GEMMA GARRISON" He defeated an Other
(겜마 개리슨 대위) 그는 실전에 데뷔하자마자 괴이을 때려눕혔다
"POWER: SCLEROKINESIS" on his first day.
(초뇌능력:경질화)
Don't let your guard down around him, Shiden.
시덴 방심하지 마
All right.
그럼
"HARUKA FRAZER, POWER: TELEPATHY" It's about to start.
(하루카 프레이저 소위 초뇌능력: 정신감응) 시작하겠어요
Ready,
Ready
go!
Go
Kasane!
카사네
Watch out for the flame!
화상을 입지 않도록 조심해
It started.
시작이다
"MAJOR KYOKA EDEN, POWER: DUPLICATION" Go for it, everyone!
(쿄카 에덴 소좌 초뇌능력: 복제) 여러분 힘내세요
Naomi, sorry about that.
미안해 나오미
It's the same trick as before.
이건 전에 썼던 그 스킬
My power is clairvoyance.
나의 초뇌능력은 미래 예지에요
I can foresee the future in an instant.
잠시 후의 미래 모습을 볼 수 있어요
I'm too lazy to move.
움직이기 싫어...
I see it.
봤어
Not bad, Gemma.
역시 겜마
You could sense me.
내 움직임을 읽어버렸네
Don't pull any punches, bring it on!
예의는 필요 없어 덤벼봐
I must get the flag!
반드시 깃발을 빼앗아야 해
Kasane, don't you remember the rules?
카사네 규칙을 잊었어
FAILURE
(실패)
VICTORY
(승리)
Arashi!
아라시
I'm exhausted.
배터리가 나갔어
This should be enough for training.
이쯤이면 훈련도 충분히 했잖아
She is quite a handful.
정말 어찌할 도리가 없군
Well done.
수고하셨어요
You did great too.
수고했어요
You're not too shabby.
예사롭지 않은데
I felt the same when we last fought together.
지난번에 함께 싸웠을 때도 그렇게 느꼈어
I appreciate the compliment.
칭찬해 줘서 감사해요…
But it takes more to earn my acknowledgment.
단 아직 인정한 건 아니야
Whether you deserve my sister or not,
과연 언니와 잘 어울릴 수 있을지는
I'll keep observing.
좀 더 지켜봐야겠어
What do you mean about observing?
뭘 지켜봐
Excuse me, I have a message.
미안 메시지가 왔어
Father?
아버지가
Congratulations on making it into the force.
정식 입대를 축하한다
I'm still against the idea of you joining OSF.
네가 토벌군에 입대하는 건 여전히 반대하지만
But at least don't get yourself hurt.
다치지 않기만을 바란다
Since you're a member of OSF now,
토벌군의 일원으로 되였으니
that means you can hold your own.
너도 혼자서 한몫을 할 수 있다는 말이다
I want to use this opportunity
이 기회에
to talk to you about our family and your late mother.
너하고 가족 일과 돌아가신 너의 어머니에 대해 얘기하련다
We'll have dinner with Kaito another day.
다음엔 카이토도 불러서 같이 식사나 하자
I'll contact you again.
다시 연락하마
Kagero, your surprised me.
카게로 정말 신기해
What is it, Tsugumi?
츠구미 어디가 신기한데
I thought you hated training.
훈련을 싫어하잖아요
We don't have new members every day.
오랜만에 신인들이 들어왔잖아
Not to mention there are more girls joining our platoon this year.
그리고 올해는 여자애들도 많아서
I have to make sure they see the awesome side of me.
멋진 모습 보여주고 싶잖아
Deployment order.
출동 명령입니다
Other activities confirmed.
괴이 출몰을 확인했습니다
The location is the abandoned railway line of Suoh Nine.
지점은 폐지하선로 스오 9호선 부근입니다
Seto Platoon and Kyoka Platoon,
세토 소대 교카 소대는
please deploy immediately.
즉시 출동해 주십시오
A lot of them fell from the Extinction Belt.
단절의 띠가 많이 떨어졌어요
The Others have got in through the air vents.
괴이는 에어컨으로 침입할 것 같아요
Communication devices might be affected here.
그으로 인해 통신 기능이 영향을 받을 수 있습니다
Relying solely on telepathy without brain talk
브레인 토크 없이 테레파시만으로
will result in a one-way communication from me.
저희 쪽에서 일방적으로 여러분에게 전달하는 것만 가능해요
Let's pray the comms will work fine.
통신 기능이 양호하게 유지되길 빕니다
Seto Platoon, move out.
좋아 세토 소대 전진
Kyoka Platoon, move out.
교카 소대 전진
Hold on, Brother.
오빠 잠깐만요
What are you planning?
오빠는 도대체 무슨 생각을 하고 있나요
What is it that you seek?
도대체 무엇을 바라고 있어요
The past and future of this country.
이 나라의 미래와 과거다
They are here!
오고 있어요
Get ready!
오고 있어
Scatter!
흩어져
Begin the attacks!
전투 시작이다
Captain, the communication disruption caused by the Extinction Belt is getting worse.
대장님 단절의 띠로 인한 통신 장애가 점점 더…
At this rate...
이대로 가다간...
Understood. How is Kyoka Platoon doing?
와타루 교카 소대의 상황은 어떠한가
Wataru?
와타루
Enemies from above, watch out!
위쪽에 괴이가... 빨리...
What was that? Haruka, repeat!
뭐라고 하루카 다시 한번 얘기해봐
They are attacking from above!
위에서부터 공격해 오고 있어요
Sister!
언니
Captain Kyoka.
교카 대장님
Arashi, Shiden!
아라시 시덴
Yuito, Nagi.
유이토 나기
It's Kasane and Naomi.
카사네 나오미
Kasane, Naomi, are you all right?
카사네 나오미 괜찮아요
Tsugumi, where are Captain Seto and the rest?
츠구미 세토대장과 그들은
We lost communication with them.
통신 기능이 연결되지 않습니다
But I know they will be fine.
하지만 분명 괜찮을 것입니다
Where are Kyoka and the rest?
교카 소대는요
They can handle this level of enemies with ease.
이 정도의 괴이는 가이 대적할 수 있을 거야
They are here!
또 오고 있어요
Naomi, watch out!
위험해 나오미
-Nagi! -Sister!
-나기 -언니
Gemma, Tsugumi!
겜마 츠구미
Is everyone all right?
다들 괜찮아
We are all right. What about the other two?
우린 괜찮아 다른 두 명은
Where are Nagi and Naomi?
나기와 나오미가...
Sister!
언니…
I found them. They are in here.
찾았어요 안에 있어요
Yuito, are you still there?
유이토 살아 있어
Nagi, where are you now?
나기 지금 어디에 있어
We're on the other side of these boulders.
돌덩이 옆이야
Naomi is with me.
나오미와 함께 있어
Nagi.
나기
What is it, Nagi?
어떻게 된 거야 나기
The enemies are here!
괴이가…
Sister!
언니
This is bad. They are surrounded by Others.
안돼 괴이의 수가 너무 많아요
Connect the SAS cable.
SAS케이블을 연결하겠어
Understood.
알았어
Let's give it a shot.
해봐
Sister!
어니
Nagi, are you all right?
나기 괜찮아
Sorry about that...
미안...
Sister!
언니
I'm all right, Kasane.
카사네 난 괜찮아
No!
안돼
Kasane?
카사네
Kasane!
카사네...
Sister...
언니…
I'm glad you're safe.
다행이야
Sister?
언니
What's wrong? Sister!
왜 그래 언니
Let's move, Karen.
카렌 빨리 가봐
♪I don't need to let fate dictate me♪
운명의 지시를 따를 필요는 없어
♪Because I believe that I can rewrite it♪
반드시 고쳐질 거라 믿어
♪I'll always be a dreamer now and forever♪
앞으로 계속 꿈을 꿀수 있도록
♪Another sunrise shines now and it blacks out♪
아침 해가 휘황찬란하게 빛나다 다시 넘어가네
♪What's waiting for us at the world's end♪
이 세상 끝에 뭐가 기다리고 있을까
♪Forever eternal, keep the fire going♪
미래의 불꽃은 영원히 꺼지지 않을 거에요
♪Who can shake us♪
누가 우리를 위협하고 있을까
♪Who can define us♪
누가 우리를 위해 결정해 줄까
♪It's nothing less than our story♪
이건 우리만의 이야기야
♪Forever eternal, keep the fire going in your heart♪
앞으로도 그대 마음속의 불꽃은 영원히 꺼지지 않을 거에요
CONSPIRACY
(음모)